

MADALINA-ELEONORA GHEORGHE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a Frontend Developer with a long experience working with Angular, RxJs, Sass, AWS Services and Azure. I delivered unique features in the past projects, improving user experience, contributing actively in meetings with suggestions and helping other colleagues, maintaining a good communication with the client. I worked with large companies, in industries like banking, insurance, retail and e-commerce.



SOFT SKILLS

Effective communication

Collaborative teamwork

Personal accountability

Time management

Creative problem-solving

Proactivity



TECHNICAL SKILLS















LANGUAGES

Romanian - Native

English - C1 Advanced



AWARDS

2nd place at Rau-DevHack Hackathon Apr 2019

1st place for Web&Mobile Challenge at DevHacks Nov 2018



FOLLOW ME

LinkedIn / Medium / GitHub - madalinaeleonorag

Scan to go to my website:





WORK EXPERIENCE

Cognizant / Bucharest

Jan 2023 - Present

Frontend Developer

Fraud monitoring internal application using Angular, TypeScript.

Deloitte Digital Romania / Bucharest Oct 2021 - Dec 2022 **Frontend Developer**

- Internal banking and insurance applications using Angular, RxJs, Sass;
- Internal banking application for client loans using React, Thymeleaf, Mambu, TypeScript, AWS Services, Java.

IBM Romania / Bucharest

Dec 2018 - Oct 2021

Frontend Developer

- Reinsurance internal applications using Angular, Ionic, TypeScript, Capacitor, RxJs;
- Public website for retail recyclable materials using React.js;
- Public e-commerce website using Angular, TypeScript, RxJs, Unit testing, AEM.

Groupe Renault / Bucharest Intern

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017

Generating statistics using Matlab, on the use of their machines, according to data received from the research team.



EDUCATION

Romanian-American University, Bucharest 2018 - 2020

Master's Degree in Computer Science for Business Management

Romanian-American University, Bucharest 2015 - 2018

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science for Business Management